icashcard.in 2016-05-06

# iCASHCARD – Privacy Policy

###  Privacy policy

   This website ("Website") and **iCashCard** are part of the **GI Technology Private Limited** Network (the "Network"), is owned and/or operated by GI Technology private Limited ("GI").on behalf of itself and its holding companies, subsidiaries and affiliates (together, "GI", “we”, "us" or "our"). At iCashCard we recognize that privacy and security of personal financial information is a concern to our customers. We have taken the utmost care in establishing and implementing policies and procedures to protect this information.

  We believe that your privacy should never be compromised. At the same time, we want to offer you the array of financial products and services you need to accomplish your financial goals. We believe we can do both by adhering to the provisions of this privacy notice. For that reason, we have developed this Privacy Policy to explain what information we collect and how we use information gathered on this website. Your visit to this website is subject to this Privacy Policy. You must be at least 18 (the age of majority) to register for an **iCashCard** account or provide other personal information to us. By browsing and using this site you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by this Privacy Agreement and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations.

#####  1\. The Information We Gather 

  In order for us to provide you with our services and products, we may collect personal information such as your name, address, phone number, date of birth, or any other information that may be required for identification purposes. The personal information that we collect depends on the products and services that are being provided or requested. If you do not provide us with the information asked, we may not be able to provide the products or services you have requested. We limit the use and collection of this information to that which is necessary to maintain and administer financial services, provide excellent service, and offer new products and services that may be of benefit to our customers. We also track information like the domain name from which you contact us, the pages you request, the products you buy, the referring site, and the time that you spend on the site. For everyone who visits our website, Sub-Merchant purchase page, we log IP addresses, the type of operating system that your computer uses, and the type of browser software used by you. From the IP address, we can determine the Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of your point of connectivity. 

#####  2\. Why we gather your information: 

  In order for us to provide you with our services and products, we may collect personal information such as your name, address, phone number, date of birth, or any other information that may be required for identification purposes. The personal information that we collect depends on the products and services that are being provided or requested. If you do not provide us with the information asked, we may not be able to provide the products or services you have requested. We limit the use and collection of this information to that which is necessary to maintain and administer financial services, provide excellent service, and offer new products and services that may be of benefit to our customers.

  We also track information like the domain name from which you contact us, the pages you request, the products you buy, the referring site, and the time that you spend on the site. For everyone who visits our website, Sub-Merchant purchase page, we log IP addresses, the type of operating system that your computer uses, and the type of browser software used by you. From the IP address, we can determine the Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of your point of connectivity.

#####  3\. Why we gather your information:

  We gather information about you and your account so we can 

  1. Deliver products and services to meet your needs,
  2. Know who you are and thereby prevent unauthorized use of your iCashCard
  3. Design and improve the products we offer,
  4. Replace a lost card, PIN, or to provide some other form of assistance, and
  5. Comply with laws and regulations that govern us.

 GI collects personal information in a number of ways, including:

  * Directly from you, such as when you provide the information by phone or email, in an application form, or when you submit your personal details to participate in our/co-partners Competition, surveys and promotions;
  * From third parties such as credit reporting agencies, our business partners that sell you iCashCard products or services, your authorised representatives or any other of the GI group of companies; or 
  * From publicly available sources of information such as telephone directories and websites.
  * **Prospect Information** \-- Our Network also collects prospect information from our users. Our users may provide another person's information, such as their friend's e-mail address, contact details etc., in order to send them content or offerings from our Network. The prospect's information is only used for the purpose for which it was submitted. The prospect information will never be shared with third party advertisers. 

#####  4\. How We Use and Disclose Your Information:

GI may use your personal information for any one or more of the following purposes:

  1. To administer your participation in the iCashCard program.
  2. To verify your identity or transactions which you may enter into with us;
  3. To provide the products and services that you request;
  4. To administer and manage the provision of our products and services;
  5. To provide customer service, such as to answer your account-related questions.
  6. To check your qualifications for registration.
  7. To verify your name, address, and other information
  8. To develop and refine our products and services.
  9. To contact you when necessary.
  10. To send you information about our programs and other promotional materials, subject to the privacy choices described below. 
  11. To conduct client surveys in order to improve the ways in which we provide you with our products and services;
  12. To conduct credit checks and to obtain ongoing credit information;
  13. To research and develop GI’ suite of products and services;
  14. To comply with laws and regulatory requirements including complying with any request made by a governmental authority in connection with legal proceedings or the prevention or detection of crime;
  15. To comply with GI’ risk management policies and procedures, including our security procedures;
  16. To train our staff;
  17. To promote and market our products and services to you and to inform you of our special offers, promotions or competitions, including by way of direct mail and telemarketing (unless you tell us otherwise);

We may use your personal information for additional purposes related to the purposes listed above. We will not, however, use your personal information other than for: 

  * a purpose made known to you;
  * a purpose you would reasonably expect;
  * a purpose required or permitted by law; or
  * a purpose otherwise authorised by you. 

We will not disclose any of your personal information to any third party outside of “GI” except: 

  * To fraud prevention agencies and other organisations who may use the information to prevent fraud and money laundering;
  * To our suppliers or service providers that process data on our behalf;
  * To the bank that issued your prepaid card (and is a member of the card scheme);
  * To persons acting as our agents (and our partners who sell our prepaid cards) under a strict code of confidentiality;
  * To anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties under our prepaid card terms and conditions with you;
  * As required by law or regulation;
  * To your employer, where the card has been provided to you for use in the course of your employment
  * For such purposes that you have given us consent to do so

Please note that we do reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information and other information that you have provided to us to our successors in business and purchasers of our site assets. 

#####  5\. Phishing emails: 

  You may receive an email claiming to be from us with a link to what appears to be our website, where you are prompted to enter your personal and account details. We are in no way involved with this email, and the website does not belong to us or our partners. 

#####  6\. Links to Other Websites: 

  **GI** may create links to third party websites. **GI** is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by websites that are linked from our website. For this reason, if you link to another website from **GI** , please consult that website’s privacy policy. 

###  7\. Opting out of marketing, promotions or related activities 

  You may be contacted by mail, telephone or email for purposes of customer service or to be notified of related products, promotions, newsletters, customer surveys and similar materials that we may conduct or distribute from time to time. If you do not wish to receive any such communications, you may advise us that you wish to opt out:

  * by mail addressed to   
GI Technology Private Limited,   
C-9,Thiruvika Industrial Estate,   
Guindy.   
Chennai.   

  * by sending an e-mail to us at [sales@icashcard.in](mailto:sales@icashcard.in)
  * by calling us at **1800-108-1080**

#####  8\. Improper Conduct

The restrictions above will not apply in the event that you engage in certain improper conduct. Specifically, GI/iCashCard shall have the right to itself use or release to third parties personally identifiable information regarding users who are suspected of having used any site or any other service in the Network for any fraudulent purposes or having otherwise violated any law, rule or regulation or the rights of third parties or having engaged in any conduct which GI/iCashCard deems improper. By using any service in the Network, you are agreeing to our use or release of any information you provide in any manner we deem appropriate or necessary if you are suspected of having engaged in any conduct which GI/iCashCard deems improper. 

#####  9\. Security 

 At **GI** security is a priority. We have implemented and maintain high security standards and procedures to safeguard against unauthorized access to your information. We employ appropriate measures to protect consumer information against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These may include, among other, encryption, physical access security and other appropriate technologies. **GI** continually reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary. Please note, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit via our online services. 

#####  10\. Cookies

  "Cookies" are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. You can find out more about the way cookies work on [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). 

 We use both our own and our partner companies’ cookies to support these activities. The cookie we give you stores your user id and tells us whether you've logged in or not. We don’t use cookies to track peoples Internet usage after leaving our sites and we don’t store personal information in them that others could read and understand. 

 Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookie function. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However if you do not accept incoming cookies then the performance of our website on your system may not be to the full standard or our website may not serve you at all. 

#####  11\. Consent  

  By returning or submitting your card application form with your personal information to us, you consent to our processing your personal data, including sensitive personal data, and to the transfer of your information to our Partner companies or to other Countries which do not provide the same level of data protection, if necessary for the above purposes. If we do make such a transfer, we will put a contract in place to ensure your information is protected. Please be aware that iCashCard/GI does not control the acts of its Merchants, agents, franchises, customers, users or visitors. 

  When you give us information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed you to act for them, to consent to the processing of their personal data, including sensitive personal data and to the transfer of their information abroad and to receive on their behalf any data protection notices. 

  This website takes measures to protect its data that contains information related to you. However, as a consideration for viewing this site or interacting with this site in any manner, you waive all claims of any nature against this site concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information. You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by others, such as "hackers," and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause harm to you and that you agree that iCashCard/GI is not responsible to provide any damages to you. This Privacy policy is subject to the laws of Union of India and Courts at Chennai alone have jurisdiction. 

  In addition, in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture, or other transfer or disposition of some or all assets of GI, or its affiliated entities, you agree that we can accordingly assign, sell, license, or transfer to third parties any information, including personally identifying information you have provided to us. By using this website, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy of GI. If you do not agree to this, please do not use our websites or services. 

#####  12\. Notification of changes 

  As changes occur in the business, technology, and laws that affect this policy, we will continue to review and revise this Privacy Policy. The use of information we gather now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use. We may send you periodic notices of changes to our policy, but you should check our website periodically to see the current policy. 

###  Contact

 If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at 

GI Technology Private Limited,  
iCashCard Division,   
C-9,Thiruvika Industrial Estate,   
Guindy.   
Chennai - 600 032 

Toll Free :- 1800-108-1080   
Email us at [sales@icashcard.in](mailto:sales@icashcard.in)

 If you wish to terminate your relationship with GI/iCashCard and wish for us to eliminate your information from our database, please contact us at [sales@icashcard.in](mailto:sales@icashcard.in) and provide your account details.
